[PHONE RlNGlNG]
- It's Mom.
- Say hi for me.
Hi, Mom. Alan wants to talk to you.
Hi, Mom. How was Dubai?
Oh, good. I'm glad you met somebody.
Yes, yes, they are a hairy people.
[STAMMERlNG] Uh, yeah,
I don't need to know any more details...
...as long as he makes you happy.
That's a detail, Mom.
Oh, no. Don't worry about your house.
I, uh, check on it every day
on my way home from work.
Yeah, no, that's why I'm the good son.
[ALAN CHUCKLES]
Well, uh, have fun with Hamid.
That's another detail, Mom.
Yeah, I'll, uh-- I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay. Bye-bye.
You haven't been to her house once,
have you?
I checked on it with Google Earth.
It's still there.
At least the roof is, anyway.
I'll just run over today
and pick up the newspapers and the mail...
...and, uh, replace the dead plants.
- You don't think she'll notice new plants?
- No.
She doesn't pay that much attention
to living things.
Remember when she had the cockatoo?
- Oh, yeah. Polly really wanted a cracker.
- Mm.
Hey, listen, as long as
you're gonna be in Beverly Hills...
...you can drop my Mercedes off
for service.
- Happy to do it.
- Hey, I don't wanna hear it.
You and your kid live here rent-free.
I don't ask for much in return so--
Charlie, Charlie. I said I'm happy to do it.
Oh.
Damn. I was all set to bust your balls.
Sorry to disappoint you.
And just so we're clear, my car is cherry.
So if you bang it, ding it, dent it
or even change the ass-print in the seat...
...just keep driving till you get to Mexico,
then bury yourself in the desert.
I understand your concern,
and trust me, I will be very careful.
You know,
you're taking all the fun out of this.
[SlGHS]
Okay. "Get car serviced." Check.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[GROANS]
Check.
- What the hell are you doing?
JAKE: Whoa!
[THUD]
- You okay?
JAKE: No.
- I landed on my ass bone.
- Sack up. You'll be fine.
Would you grab my sunglasses
while you're down there?
"Recover sunglasses." Check.
Here.
Thanks.
- So, what's so interesting over there?
- Nothing.
Hey, you know the rule:
If there's topless sunbathers,
you don't hang out and stare at them.
You come get your Uncle Charlie.
Nobody's topless.
Oh.
Then what are you looking at?
Son of a bitch.
Uncheck.
- Just some new neighbors.
- New neighbors, huh?
What's the deal?
They making s'mores on the barbecue?
- No.
- Chicken?
It has nothing to do with food.
Oh, a girl. She cute?
No, I'm hanging off the balcony
to look at a mutant.
Don't get snippy.
I was just showing an interest.
Why don't you go
and introduce yourself?
- I can't do that. I'd look desperate.
- You are desperate.
- Come on, we'll both go.
- Really?
Ah, why not?
I got a little window before my next nap.
JAKE: Thanks.
- No problem.
- What am I gonna say?
- I don't know. Try saying hello.
"Hello"? That's all you got?
That's all I got that you can use.
I should've peed before we left.
[CHARLlE SlGHS]
You've just got a nervous bladder.
Wait till you turn 40. You'll feel like
you have to pee while you're still peeing.
- You ready to do this?
- No.
Oh, come on,
what's the worst that could happen?
She laughs at me?
Oh, that is so sweet.
No, the worst thing that could happen...
...is she falls in love with you,
you get married, 10, 12 years later...
...she leaves you, takes all your stuff,
and you have to go live in your car.
- Whoa.
- Yeah.
[DOORBELL RlNGS]
What kind of car do you think I'll have?
- Hello.
- Hi. I'm Charlie Harper. This is Jake.
We live next door, right, Jake?
- I'm Jake.
- Hi. I'm Celeste.
I'm Jake.
JEROME: Honey, is that the cable guy?
- No, Dad. It's our neighbors.
Jerome Burnett.
Hi. Charlie Harper.
This is my nephew. We just came by
to welcome you to the neighborhood.
- Well, that was very nice of you.
- Yeah. Welcome to the neighborhood. Bye.
Hang on, hang on.
- Do you know who this man is?
- Yeah, her dad. Bye.
This is Jerome Burnett,
one of the great NFL players of all time.
You're very kind. Thank you.
- You know what his nickname was, Jake?
- No.
Tell him.
[JEROME CHUCKLES]
Mad Dog.
That's great. Can I use your bathroom?
- Honey, show him where it is.
- Come on, Jake.
Lady in the house, Jake.
Put the seat back down.
- What have you been up to?
- Oh, still working for the Chargers.
- You know, mostly front-office stuff.
- Really?
So you probably have access
to tickets and such.
- I do. Do you want me to hook you up?
- Oh, jeez. I don't want to impose.
I just came by to say hello.
Can you get me a skybox?
- I'll see what I can do.
- That'd be great.
And I'm guessing if a player got injured,
you'd probably be one of the first to know.
You know, even before the, uh--
What do you call them?
--bookies?
Don't push it, Charlie.
Hey, Dad, would it be all right
if Jake and I take a walk on the beach?
- Well, sure. Why not?
- Thanks. See you later.
Isn't that nice?
That boy touches my daughter,
I'm gonna be touching you.
Understood. Ahem.
Can I use your bathroom?
- Here you go, Mr. Harper.
- Oh. Oh, thank you.
Mm. Cappuccino.
Wonder what they're serving
at the domestic dealerships.
They do take good care of you here.
Of course, they ought to,
considering what we paid for our cars.
- Oh, yeah. They are expensive.
- ls that your CL65 outside?
Uh, yes, it is mine.
How do you like it?
Pfft, what's not to like?
Does everything but trim your toenails.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Or maybe it does
and I just haven't found the button yet.
[CHUCKLES]
Not that I need to trim my toenails.
Did them last night.
Over the tub.
Clip, ping. Clip, ping.
Diane.
Oh, Alan.
[BOTH LAUGH]
- So you live around here, Alan?
- Uh, no, I live, uh, by the beach.
- Santa Monica?
- Uh, Malibu.
Ooh, Malibu.
[ALAN CHUCKLES]
Yep. Malibu.
Yeah, uh, we just call it the Boo.
You know, like,
"Hey, how are things down at the Boo? "
- Mr. Harper, your car is ready.
- Oh, uh, thank you. I'll, uh, be right there.
Well, uh, looks like I'm all done here.
Guess I'll, uh, head back to the Boo.
Don't rub it in.
They told me I'd be here all day.
- Oh, that's terrible.
- And I'm starving.
Oh, well, they have, uh, little croissants
and the, uh, chocolate-chip cookies.
Or, uh...
...maybe I could take you out
for a nice lunch.
- That would be lovely, Alan. Thank you.
- Oh, terrific. Let's go.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
This never happened with the Volvo.
[DOORBELL RlNGS]
It's 5:00.
Thanks.
I almost slept through happy hour.
Where's my little girl?
- They're not back yet?
- Why else would I be here?
Honestly, I was thinking happy hour.
Let me give Jake a call,
see what's keeping them.
Yeah, you do that.
- Did you try calling your daughter?
- She left her cell phone at the house.
[SCOFFS]
Kids, huh?
It's ringing.
[CELL PHONE RlNGlNG]
Yo, bitch, I'm gonna slap you up
Yo, bitch, I'll slap you up
Oh, that's unfortunate on so many levels.
[CELL PHONE RlNGlNG]
The way you do to everything
Put my gun inside your mouth
Got a.45 Magnum
Wanna do it...
Yo, bitch, I'm gonna slap you up
Yo, bitch, I'll slap you up
I'm talking to you, bitch
Check it
You my dream, like chocolate cream
Girl next door make you hornier...
Last all night
It's better than the fight
Yo, bitch, I'm gonna slap you up
Yo, bitch, I'll slap you up
ALAN: This is just my pied-à-terre.
DlANE: Oh.
I spend most of my time
out at the beach house.
Looks like you haven't been here
in a while.
ALAN:
Oh, just two weeks.
Don't you have someone
to come in and water your plants?
Uh, I do, but he's incredibly unreliable.
- My brother.
- Oh.
Bit of a mooch.
So now that we're here,
what do you wanna do?
[STAMMERlNG]
Uh, gee, I don't know, uh--
Oh. Well, that's an option.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[PHONE RlNGlNG THE 5TH DlMENSlON'S
"UP, UP AND AWAY"]
Oh.
Oh, excuse me.
Uh, Alan Harper speaking.
[WHlSPERlNG]
I know who's speaking, you dillweed.
We got a problem here.
Oh, really? Heh, heh.
It's the mooch at the Boo.
[ALAN CHUCKLES]
So, uh, what's the problem?
Not the wine cellar again, is it?
What the hell are you talking about,
you gibbering moron?
Oh, good, good.
Listen to me,
your idiot son's about to get me killed.
Oh, so he's okay?
He's great. Probably having the time
of his life. I'm the one in trouble.
[STAMMERlNG]
Uh, well, uh, I trust you to take care of it.
Thanks for the update.
Take a bottle of Pinot for yourself.
Alan.
Oh.
[SlGHS]
God. I thought there was an eclipse.
Excuse me,
I need to go to the bathroom again.
[BOTH MOANlNG]
[BOTH YELP AND LAUGH]
Oh, I knew it. You're married.
Oh, no, no, no. I'm not married.
This is, uh, this is just, uh, a--
A silk evening gown.
Actually, I think it's chiffon.
- Men are all the same.
- No, no, no. Wait. Diane, Diane. Uh--
[SlGHS]
You've got the wrong idea.
There's something you don't know.
- You're gay?
- No.
- You're a cross-dresser?
- No, uh--
Because, you know,
I could really get into that.
Yes.
I am a big old cross-dresser.
Sorry it took so long.
Had a little accident. Ahem.
Come on, you and me
are gonna go find those kids.
Jerome. Jerome, hang on.
- What?
- Oh.
Still pretty nimble.
Let's sit down, take a deep breath
and talk this through for a minute.
Come on, big fella.
Please?
Make it quick.
Okay, here's the deal.
Jake is harmless.
You don't have a thing to worry about.
Unless your daughter
is made out of doughnuts.
[CHARLlE CHUCKLES]
Which I'm assuming she's not.
Look, Celeste is all I've got. You don't
know what it's like being a single father.
You're right, I don't.
But I do know what it's like
to exploit women with daddy issues.
What the hell are you talking about?
Believe me, if you don't trust your daughter
to make her own decisions...
...if you try to control her life,
she's gonna grow up to resent you.
And the next thing you know,
she'll be trying to punish you...
...by going out with some
weaselly little con artist like, well, me.
And you can't kill us all.
I can try.
Okay, let me start again.
ALAN:
Are you sure this is what you want?
Yeah, baby.
It's always been one of my fantasies.
ALAN:
Okay. Just a little heads-up...
...I'm wearing the panties,
but I'm not bikini-safe.
Ugh, my ass looks huge in this.
Diane?
[CAR ENGlNE REVS]
[TlRES SQUEAL]
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
Oh, no.
Not bad.
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
Yes. Yes. My car has been stolen.
Yes, just now. If you hurry, you can ca--
Sure, I'll hold.
EVELYN:
Why am I not surprised?
Did it have to be my red chiffon?
[SOBBlNG]
Then, after I blew out my knee...
...my wife left me.
Oh, man. I'm sorry.
For a place kicker.
- Ooh, insult to injury.
- A little tiny dude from Serbia.
Not a single vowel in his entire name.
Oh, yeah, Grl Zrbnck.
That guy could sure split the uprights.
In a football manner of speaking.
[SNlFFS]
And ever since then,
it's just been me and Celeste.
Sure, sure.
I don't know what I'd do
if anything ever happened to her, Charlie.
I'd go crazy.
I'd go crazy just thinking about it.
Well, then, for God's sake,
don't think about it.
Come on. Come on. Let's get you home.
- Thanks, Charlie. You're okay.
- No problem.
You just kick back and relax. And when
Celeste walks through that door...
...all you gotta do
is act like nothing's happened.
- You think something happened?
- No, no, no. Nothing happened.
Which is why it's not really acting.
And it'll show your daughter
that you trust her.
- Okay, I'll give it a shot.
- You won't be sorry, I promise.
Okay.
Hey, come over to the house.
I got a couple of tickets for Sunday's game
I wanna lay on you.
Oh, you don't have to do that.
I'll just grab my keys. Okay, let's go.
What ever happened to the guy
you tackled in the Tampa Bay game?
Uh, Robinson. He's walking again.
JEROME:
Celeste?
Oh. Hi, Dad.
[STAMMERS]
Hey, Mr. Mad Dog.
Am I gonna be walking again?
Listen, Jake.
I'm real proud that you stepped up
and got a little action tonight...
- ...but I gotta ask you something.
- What?
Are you out of your freaking mind?
I'm sorry. We just lost track of time.
Yeah, well, thanks to you, I gotta change
my shorts for the second time today.
There's my phone.
- Who are you calling?
- Celeste.
No, no, no. Cool it with Celeste.
And change your ringtone.
[KNOCKlNG ON DOOR]
Ah, now what?
I'll be with you in a minute.
Jake, go to your room.
No matter what you hear, do not come out.
- What?
- Just go.
[SlGHS]
Look, I spoke to the kid.
He's not gonna bother
your daughter anymore.
So whatever you gotta do, do it to me.
JEROME:
I'm sorry, buddy.
- I overreacted.
- Okay.
Celeste told me everything.
She told me your boy was a gentleman
and that she wanted to kiss him.
She wanted to kiss him?
You may have bigger problems
than you thought.
Hey, here's two tickets for the game.
You take Jake, I'll bring Celeste.
We'll make a day of it.
Thanks. That's great.
- Excuse me.
- Sorry.
Okay. Well, see you Sunday.
[SlGHS]
Alan, where's my car?
Why are you wearing a dress? Alan?
[KNOCKlNG ON DOOR]
Why aren't you in Mexico?